{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"8660/66",
			"answer":"8660/66",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3828/33",
			"answer":"3828/33",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3614/25",
			"answer":"3614/25",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1691/31",
			"answer":"1691/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4388/89",
			"answer":"4388/89",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"27.44/0.28",
			"answer":"27.44/0.28",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"119.7/57",
			"answer":"119.7/57",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"2.537/0.43",
			"answer":"2.537/0.43",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"45.12/94",
			"answer":"45.12/94",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"172.5/23",
			"answer":"172.5/23",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}